stackstorm.com 2017-07-24

# Privacy Policy - StackStorm

Effective Date: May 12, 2015

StackStorm, Inc. (“StackStorm”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) recognizes the importance of privacy. In this Privacy Policy, we describe how we collect, use, and disclose information that we obtain about visitors to our website, stackstorm.com (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy does not address our collection, use, or disclosure practices with regard to information collected through any of our platforms.

By visiting the Site, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Privacy Policy. Your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service (“Terms”), including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. Our Terms are incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy.

Information We Collect  
How We Use Your Information  
How We Disclose Your Information  
Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms  
Third-Party Ad Networks  
User-Generated Content  
Third-Party Links  
Security  
Your Choices  
Children  
Special Information for California Consumers  
Contact Us  
Changes to this Privacy Policy

## Information We Collect

We collect information about you directly from you, from third parties, and automatically through your use of our Site. We may combine information automatically collected with other information that we have collected about you.

  * **Information We Collect Directly From You.** We collect information from you when you sign up for product updates, sign up for our newsletter, request information from us, post to our blog, participate in a survey, and otherwise interact with our Site. The type of information that we collect from you depends upon your particular interaction with our Site and may include your name, email address, company name, and any other information that you choose to provide to us.
  * **Information We Collect from Third Parties.** We also may collect information about you from marketing sources and public records. We may combine this information with other information that we collect about you.
  * **Information We Collect Automatically.** We and our third party service providers automatically collect information such as the following about your use of our Site through cookies and other technologies: domain name; browser type; operating system type; pages or screens you view; links you click; IP address; when and the length of time you visit or use our Site; and the referring URL, or the webpage that led you to our Site.

## How We Use Your Information

We may use your information, including personal information, for the following purposes:

  * **Providing Our Services.** To provide our services to you, to fulfill your orders, and for other customer service purposes.Tailoring Content. To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using our Site or services.
  * **Communicating with You.** To communicate with you, including via email, about your use of our services; to respond to your inquiries; to provide you with news and newsletters.
  * **For Marketing and Advertising.** To notify you (including through email) about our products and services we think may interest you and for other marketing, advertising, and promotional purposes.
  * **Analyzing Use of Our Services.** To better understand how users access and use our Site, both on an aggregated and individualized basis; to respond to user desires and preferences; and for other research and analytical purposes.
  * **Complying with the Law.** To comply with applicable legal obligations.

## How We Disclose Your Information

We may your information that we collect about you, including personal information, with the following entities:

  * **Affiliates.** We may disclose your information to our affiliates or subsidiaries for research, marketing, and other purposes consistent with this Policy.
  * **Service Providers.** We may disclose your information to our vendors, service providers, agents, or others who perform functions on our behalf.
  * **Unaffiliated Third Parties.** We may disclose your information to other unaffiliated third parties, including for their own marketing purposes. Please see our Special Information for California Consumers section below with regard to such disclosures.

We may also disclose your information that we collect about you, including personal information, in the following ways:

  * **Business Transfers.** We may disclose your information to another entity if we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding.
  * **In Response to Legal Process.** We may disclose your information in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, subpoena, court order, or other legal process.
  * **To Protect Us and Others.** We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms or this Privacy Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.
  * **Aggregate and De-Identified Information.** We may disclose aggregate or de-identified information about users for marketing, advertising, research, or similar purposes.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms

We and our service providers use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track information about your use of our Site. We or our service providers may combine this information with other personal information we collect about you.

**Do Not Track.** Our Site does not respond to Do Not Track signals and we or our service providers may track your activities once you leave our Site. You may disable certain tracking as discussed in this section (e.g., by disabling cookies) and as discussed below with regard to the use of third party ad networks.

**Cookies.** We or our service providers may use cookies to track visitor activity on our Site. A cookie is a text file that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We or our service providers may use cookies to track user activities on our Site, such as the pages visited and time spent on our Site. Most browsers allow users to refuse cookies. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Visitors to our Site who disable cookies may not be able to browse certain areas of the Site.

**Third-Party Analytics.** We use third-party service providers, including Google Analytics, to evaluate the use of our Site and services. We or our service providers use automated devices and applications to evaluate use of our Site. We or our service providers use these tools to help us improve our Site, services, performance, and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies, such as web beacons or Flash LSO, to perform their services.

## Third-Party Ad Networks

We use third parties such as network advertisers to display advertisements on third-party websites, and to evaluate the success of our advertising campaigns. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to particular websites. This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements by displaying ads for products and services in which you might be interested. Third-party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors, and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this Policy. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information about your usage of our Site and Services, as well as aggregate or non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our Site and users of our Services.

You may opt out of many third-party ad networks, including those operated by members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”). For more information regarding this practice by NAI members and DAA members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including how to opt out of third-party ad networks operated by NAI and DAA members, please visit their respective websites: www.networkadvertising.org/choices (NAI) and www.aboutads.info/choices (DAA).

Opting out of one or more NAI member or DAA member networks (many of which will be the same) only means that those members no longer will deliver targeted content or ads to you. It does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content or ads at all. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your NAI or DAA opt-out may no longer be effective. Additional information is available on NAI’s and DAA’s websites accessible by the above links.  

## User-Generated Content

Portions of our Site, such as our blog, invite user content. If you post your own content on our Site, the contents of your post, and your user name, may be available to all visitors to our Site, and we cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy. Similarly, if you use our Site to communicate with our email groups, we cannot prevent any information that you email from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy.  

## Third-Party Links

Our Site and Services may contain links to third-party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third-party websites. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third-party websites.  

## Security

We have taken steps to help protect the information we collect about you from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security. You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your account by, among other things, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess and keeping your log-in and password private. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.  

## Your Choices

You may modify the information that you have submitted by emailing us at moc.mrotskcatsnull@troppus.

We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you. You may opt out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the email. Please note that it may take up to ten (10) business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you emails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us.  

## Children

Our Site is not designed for children under thirteen (13) years of age. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will promptly delete such information from our systems.  

## Special Information for California Consumers

California residents may request a list of certain third parties to which we have disclosed personally identifiable information about you for their own direct marketing purposes. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response. You may request this information in writing by contacting us at: moc.mrotskcatsnull@troppus. Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response.  

## Contact Us

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our Site, please contact us at moc.mrotskcatsnull@troppus.  

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on our Site. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Site.
